<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- Categories -->
    <string name="basic_info">Basic information</string>
    <string name="sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="nature_and_culture">Nature &amp; Culture</string>
    <string name="shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="communicate">Communicate</string>
    <string name="basic_korean">Basic Korean</string>
    <string name="detail">Detail</string>

    <!-- String for nav_header_main -->
    <string name="seoul_travel">Seoul Travel</string>

    <!-- String for content description -->
    <string name="attraction_image_des">Attraction Image</string>
    <string name="image_des">Image</string>

    <!-- Strings for intent -->
    <string name="image_id">image ID</string>
    <string name="name">name</string>
    <string name="short_description">short description</string>
    <string name="description">description</string>
    <string name="address">address</string>
    <string name="transport">transport</string>
    <string name="phone">phone</string>
    <string name="web">web</string>
    <string name="hours">hours</string>
    <string name="fee">fee</string>

    <!-- Basic information -->
    <string name="seoul">Seoul</string>
    <string name="seoul_des">Seoul is the capital and largest city of South Korea, and it has a
        population of around 10 million, which is one-fifth of the total population. Seoul is the
        center of politics, economy, business, education, and culture for South Korea.\n\nSeoul is a
        city where the traditional and modern coexist. Five Grand Palaces including Deoksugung,
        a UNESCO heritage site, and Bukchon Hanok Village represent a fascinating blend of ancient
        traditions. The Dongdaemun Design Plaza and Lotte World Tower are the extraordinary landmarks
        that reflect modern Seoul.\n\nThe Han River flows into the center of the city, and beautifully
        landscaped parks alongside the Han River provides an environmentally-friendly place
        where city folk can take a rest.</string>

    <!-- Basic information about climate -->
    <string name="climate">Climate</string>
    <string name="climate_des">In spring, it is warm enough during the day, but it gets chilly at night.
        In summer, it is really hot and humid(25 ~ 35°C). There is a rainy season from late June
        to early July. It is hottest in the late July and early August. In autumn, it is clear and
        dry(10 ~ 25°C). The fall foliage reaches a peak in mid-October. In winter, it is too cold.
        (-10 ~ 10°C) December and January are coldest months. </string>

    <!-- Basic information about currency -->
    <string name="currency">Currency</string>
    <string name="currency_des">Won is the Korean currency of money. One dollar (USD) is worth
        about 1,000 won.</string>

    <!-- Basic information about transportation -->
    <string name="from_incheon_to_seoul">Easy way to get from Incheon Airport to Seoul </string>
    <string name="from_incheon_to_seoul_des">The airport railroad or AREX is a very convenient way
        to get from the airport to various locations in Seoul. There are two trains that you can
        take.\n\nOne is the Express Train which goes straight to Seoul Station without any stops.
        Going on this train takes 43 minutes and is presently on sale for 8,000 won.\n\nThe other
        train goes to Seoul Station as well but makes stops at various subway transfer stations
        along the way. This training takes just over 50 minutes to go to Seoul Station and costs
        4,300 won to go to Seoul Station, or less if you get off and transfer earlier.</string>

    <!-- Sights and Landmarks -->
    <!-- Gyeongbokgoung -->
    <string name="gyeongbokgung">Gyeongbokgung Palace</string>
    <string name="gyeongbokgung_short">Gyeongbokgung Palace is the royal palace of Joseon Dynasty
        built in 1395. It is the largest and most significant of Seoul's Five Grand Palaces.</string>
    <string name="gyeongbokgung_des">Gyeongbokgung Palace was the first of the five palaces built
        in the Joseon Dynasty (1395). It was destroyed by Japanese Invasion of Korea(1592) but rebuilt
        during King Kojong(1867). During the Japanese colonial period(1910-1945), much of the palace was
        destroyed by Japan and Japanese governor-general of Korea was built in the palace. The
        restoration projects have been promoted since 1989.</string>
    <string name="gyeongbokgung_address">161 Sajik-ro, Sejongno, Jongno-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="gyeongbokgung_transport">Gyeongbokgung Station (Subway Line 3), Exit 5</string>
    <string name="gyeongbokgung_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;3700&#8211;3900</string>
    <string name="gyeongbokgung_web">royalpalace.go.kr (Korean, English)</string>
    <string name="gyeongbokgung_hours">Opening hours vary depending on the season. 
        ※ Closed on Tuesdays \n※ You can see Royal Guard Changing Ceremonies at 10:00 and 14:00</string>
    <string name="gyeongbokgung_fee">Adults : 3,000 won</string>

    <!-- Bukchon Hanok Village -->
    <string name="bukchon_hanok">Bukchon Hanok Village</string>
    <string name="bukchon_hanok_short">Bukchon Hanok Village is a good place to get a quick intro
        to old Korea. This traditional village is located between Gyeongbok Palace, Changdeok Palace.</string>
    <string name="bukchon_hanok_des">Bukchon was a high-class residential area that prime ministers,
        the royal family inhabited in Joseon Dynasty(1392–1897). The village is composed of many
        traditional houses, called Hanok and has a history of 600 years. There are museums, craft
        workshops which allows visitors to experience traditional culture.</string>
    <string name="bukchon_hanok_address">37, Gyedong-gil, Jongno-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="bukchon_hanok_transport">Anguk Station (Subway Line 3), Exit 1 or 2</string>
    <string name="bukchon_hanok_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;2148&#8211;4160</string>
    <string name="bukchon_hanok_web">hanok.seoul.go.kr </string>
    <string name="bukchon_hanok_hours">Open all year round</string>
    <string name="bukchon_hanok_fee">Free</string>

    <!-- Changdeokgung -->
    <string name="changdeokgung">Changdeokgung Palace and Huwon</string>
    <string name="changdeokgung_short">Changdeok Palace was the second palace built in 1405
        after Gyeongbokgung. Chagdeokgung is one of the UNESCO World Heritage Sites.</string>
    <string name="changdeokgung_des">Changdeok Palace is the palace where the kings of the
        Joseon Dynasty lived for the longest time. It represents the atypical beauty of Korean palace
        architecture by arranging the buildings along the mountains. It is relatively well preserved
        in its original form and its harmonious arrangement with nature is excellent. \n\n
        You can see Changdeokgung Palace by moonlight and hear historical information from a guide
        on an evening tour. This moonlight tour is held in spring and fall and you must book the
        ticket online in advance.(ticket.interpark.com/Global)\n\n
        You can visit Huwon(Secret Garden) by making a reservation on the homepage from 10:00 6 days
        before the desired visit date. </string>
    <string name="changdeokgung_address">99, Yulgok-ro, Waryong-dong, Jongno-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="changdeokgung_transport">Anguk Station (Subway Line 3), Exit 3</string>
    <string name="changdeokgung_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;3668&#8211;2300</string>
    <string name="changdeokgung_web">eng.cdg.go.kr</string>
    <string name="changdeokgung_hours">Opening hours vary depending on the season. ※ Closed on Mondays</string>
    <string name="changdeokgung_fee">Adults : 3,000 won</string>

    <!-- N Seoul Tower -->
    <string name="n_seoul_tower">N Seoul Tower</string>
    <string name="n_seoul_tower_short">N Seoul Tower is one of the symbolic landmarks of Seoul.
        Located on the Namsan Mountain, it provides an amazing 360-degree view of Seoul.</string>
    <string name="n_seoul_tower_des">The N Seoul tower was  first established as a broadcast
        tower to send out TV and radio signals in 1969. As of now, it has become one of the
        representative landmarks and multi-cultural venues in Seoul. There is a cable car that makes
        it easy to access, but the walk up through the park gives you beautiful sights to see.
    </string>
    <string name="n_seoul_tower_address">105, Namsangongwon-gil, Yongsan-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="n_seoul_tower_transport">[Cable Car] Myeong-dong Station (Subway Line 4),
        Exit 3</string>
    <string name="n_seoul_tower_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;3455&#8211;9277</string>
    <string name="n_seoul_tower_web">seoultower.co.kr/en/</string>
    <string name="n_seoul_tower_hours">10:00~23:00</string>
    <string name="n_seoul_tower_fee">[Observatory] 10,000 won</string>

    <!-- Cheonggyecheon -->
    <string name="cheonggyecheon">Cheonggyecheon Stream</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_short">Cheonggyecheon Stream is popular places for those
        seeking recreation and a variety of performances.</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_des">In the Cheonggyecheon, large and small events are held
        almost every week. There is also a music performance and a movie screening day. \n\n
        Cheonggyecheon Stream passes close to Deoksugung Palace, Seoul Plaza, the Sejong Center,
        Insadong Street, Changdeokgung Palace, and Changgyeonggung Palace, allowing visitors to easily
        visit major tourist sites after a leisure stroll along the stream.
        </string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_address">Cheonggyecheon-ro, Sangwangsimni-dong, Jongno-gu,
        Seoul</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_transport">City Hall Station (Subway Line 1, 2), Exit 4.
        Walk 250 m north to Cheonggye Plaza. </string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;2290&#8211;7111</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_web">english.visitkorea.or.kr</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_hours">Open 24 hours</string>
    <string name="cheonggyecheon_fee">Free</string>

    <!-- The War Memorial of Korea -->
    <string name="war_memorial">The War Memorial of Korea</string>
    <string name="war_memorial_short">The War Memorial of Korea, located in Yongsan-gu, Seoul,
        exhibits and preserve materials related to the Korean War and serves as a national moral
        educational venue.</string>
    <string name="war_memorial_des">The War Memorial of Korea was established to commemorate the
        noble sacrifice of patriotic martyrs by the War Memorial Service Korea Society on June 10, 1994.
        The museum houses approximately 33,000 artifacts with about 10,000 on display at an indoor and
        outside exhibition halls.\n\nThere are six separate indoor halls, including Expeditionary Forces Room,
        Patriotic Memorial Room, War History Room, 6·25 Korean War Room, Development Hall and Large
        Machinery Room. The outdoor exhibition hall showcases large-sized weapons.</string>
    <string name="war_memorial_address">29, Itaewon-ro, Yongsan-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="war_memorial_transport">Samgakji Station(Subway Line 4, 6), Exit 12</string>
    <string name="war_memorial_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;709&#8211;3139</string>
    <string name="war_memorial_web">www.warmemo.or.kr</string>
    <string name="war_memorial_hours">09:00 ~ 18:00 ※ Closed on Mondays</string>
    <string name="war_memorial_fee">Free</string>

    <!-- Lotte World Tower -->
    <string name="lotte_world_tower">Lotte World Tower</string>
    <string name="lotte_world_tower_short">The Lotte World Tower is a supertall skyscraper
        with a 123-floor, 555 m-high. It opened to the public on April 3, 2017 and is the fifth
        tallest building in the world as of today.</string>
    <string name="lotte_world_tower_des">Lotte World Tower was designed with a conceptual design
        drawing inspiration from Korean ceramics and Korean writing brushes. The tower contains
        galleries, cafes, and a luxury hotel, in addition to a sky walk and an observation deck.
        It will be one of the best spots to appreciate the breathtaking view of Seoul's vibrant
        city lights.</string>
    <string name="lotte_world_tower_address"> 300, Olympic-ro, Songpa-gu, Seoul(Sincheon-dong 29)</string>
    <string name="lotte_world_tower_transport">Jamsil Station (Subway Line 2), Exit 2
        \nJamsil Station(Subway Line 8 ), Exit 11</string>
    <string name="lotte_world_tower_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;3213&#8211;5000</string>
    <string name="lotte_world_tower_web">www.lwt.co.kr</string>
    <string name="lotte_world_tower_hours">09:30 ~ 23:00</string>
    <string name="lotte_world_tower_fee">Adults : 27,000 won (Fast Pass: 50,000 won)</string>

    <!-- Bongeunsa Temple -->
    <string name="bongeunsa">Bongeunsa Temple</string>
    <string name="bongeunsa_short">Bongeunsa Temple is a Buddhist temple located across the road from
        COEX mall and was founded in the 10th year of Silla King Weongseong's reign (794). </string>
    <string name="bongeunsa_des">Bongeunsa Temple is once known as Gyeonseongsa Temple. In 1498,
        Queen Jeonghyeon refurbished Gyeonseongsa Temple at the east of King Seongjong\'s royal
        mausoleum and renamed the temple as Bongeunsa.
        \nTemple Stay \nTea Ceremony Experience, Temple Tour, 108 Bows, Buddhist Aervice, Buddhist Meal,
        Interacting with monks and etc.</string>
    <string name="bongeunsa_address">531, Bongeunsa-ro, Gangnam-gu, Seoul(Samseong-dong)</string>
    <string name="bongeunsa_transport">Bongeunsa Temple Station (Subway Line 9), Exit 1\n
        Samseong Station (Subway Line 2), Exit 6</string>
    <string name="bongeunsa_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;3218&#8211;4800</string>
    <string name="bongeunsa_web">temple.bongeunsa.org/public_html_en/</string>
    <string name="bongeunsa_hours">Open all year round</string>
    <string name="bongeunsa_fee">Free</string>

    <!-- Insadong -->
    <string name="insadong">Insadong</string>
    <string name="insadong_short">Insa-dong is an important place where old but precious and
        traditional goods are on display.  There is one main road in Insa-dong with alleys on each
        side. Within these alleys are galleries and traditional restaurants, tea houses, and cafes.
</string>
    <string name="insadong_des">Insadong is one of the must-visit neighborhoods in Seoul.
        You can experience various traditions, such as making crafts using traditional Hanji
        (traditional handmade paper), trying on Hanbok, making Kimchi.\n\nThere are lots of galleries
        that show traditional Korean fine art. On the main street and each alley are lots of buildings of
        arts, crafts, shops, traditional cafes. </string>
    <string name="insadong_address">62, Insadong-gil, Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="insadong_transport">Anguk Station (Subway Line 3), Exit 6\n
        Jonggak Station (Subway Line 1), Exit 3</string>
    <string name="insadong_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;734&#8211;0222</string>
    <string name="insadong_web">www.hiinsa.com/eng/</string>
    <string name="insadong_hours">Open all year round</string>
    <string name="insadong_fee">Free</string>

    <!-- Dongdaemun Design Plaza (DDP) -->
    <string name="ddp">Dongdaemun design plaza</string>
    <string name="ddp_short">Dongdaemun Design Plaza (DDP) holds various exhibitions, fashion
        shows, forums, conferences, and other various cultural events.</string>
    <string name="ddp_des">Dongdaemun Design Plaza opened in March 2014 is a multi-cultural complex.
        There are various facilities such as Art halls, Museum, Design Lab, Dongdaemun History
        &amp; Culture Park. DDP provides diverse contents to experience new design. \n
        The DDP was designed by Zaha Hadid. She focused on the dynamism fo the Dongdaemun area,
        which is in a state of constant flux from the early morning to late at night. \n
        In the night(Fri. Sat. 18:00 ~23:00), Youth Runway Market opens at DDP. You can enjoy diverse
        foods or exciting performances.</string>
    <string name="ddp_address">281, Eulji-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="ddp_transport">Dongdaemun History &amp; Culture Park Station (Subway
        Line 2, 4 ,5), Exit 1</string>
    <string name="ddp_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;2153&#8211;0408</string>
    <string name="ddp_web">www.ddp.or.kr</string>
    <string name="ddp_hours">[Museum] 10:00~21:00 ※ Closed on Mondays</string>
    <string name="ddp_fee">Prices vary depending on the exhibition</string>

    <!-- Hongik University Street -->
    <string name="hongik_uni_street">Hongik University Street</string>
    <string name="hongik_uni_street_short">Hongik University Street (also called Hongdae Street)
        is known for underground music, clubs, cafes, fashion and art festivals.</string>
    <string name="hongik_uni_street_des">Hongdae Street is a energetic neighborhood where lots
        of young people hang out especially at night. There are lots of street performances, fashion
        shops, live cafes, restaurants, bars, and clubs.\n\nHongdae Walking Street is a main spot of
        Hongdae area which has an outdoor stage for indie band performance and dynamic culture of
        young people. </string>
    <string name="hongik_uni_street_address">Seogyo-dong, Mapo-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="hongik_uni_street_transport">Hongik University Station (Subway Line 2,
        Gyeongui-Jungang, AREX), Exit 8 or 9</string>
    <string name="hongik_uni_street_phone">Hongdae Tourist Information Center :
        +82&#8211;2&#8211;3153&#8211;8363</string>

    <!-- Jongmyo Shrine-->
    <string name="jongmyo">Jongmyo Shrine</string>
    <string name="jongmyo_short">Jongmyo is a royal shrine dedicated to the performance of
        ancestral rites for the deceased kings and queens of the Joseon Dynasty. Jongmyo is one of
        the UNESCO World Heritage Sites.</string>
    <string name="jongmyo_des">Being the place where the royal ancestral tablets are enshrined,
        Jongmyo\'s atmosphere is solemn and sacred rather than splendid like the royal palaces. The
        simple and elegant buildings of this shrine have faithfully kept their original forms since
        the 16th century. </string>
    <string name="jongmyo_address">157, Jong-ro, Jongno-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="jongmyo_transport">Jongno3(sam)-ga Station (Subway Line 1, 3, 5), Exit 11</string>
    <string name="jongmyo_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;765&#8211;0195\nKorea Travel Hotline: +82&#8211;2&#8211;1330</string>
    <string name="jongmyo_web">jm.cha.go.kr</string>
    <string name="jongmyo_hours">English Guide tour - 10:00 12:00 14:00 16:00 ※ Closed on Tuesdays</string>
    <string name="jongmyo_fee">Adults : 1,000 won</string>

    <!-- Tours & Nature & Culture -->
    <!--DMZ tour -->
    <string name="dmz">Demilitarized Zone (DMZ) Tour</string>
    <string name="dmz_short">The Korean Demilitarized Zone (DMZ) is a border zone that divides
        the Korean Peninsula into South Korea and North Korea. </string>
    <string name="dmz_des">The Demilitarized Zone (DMZ) is a buffer zone, which was established
        on July 27, 1953, when the Armistice Agreement was signed during the Korean War. The DMZ
        vividly captures the scars and wounds of the Korean War as well as the wishes and hopes for
        the future.\n\nDMZ extends largely from Gyeonggi-do to Gangwon-do, it is advised to make a plan in advance
        for which region you are most interested in visiting. The Major DMZ tourist destinations in
        Gyeonggi-do are Imjingak Resort, The Third Tunnel, Dorasan Station, Panmunjeom (Joint Security Area),
        Unification Hill and Yeolsoe Observatory.\n\nMore importantly, you are required to bring a
        legitimate form of identification and/or your passport when going to the DMZ.\n\nVisitors can
        only access Panmunjeom by joining a DMZ packaged tour provided by approved travel agencies.</string>
    <string name="dmz_web">DMZ in Gyeonggi-do: english.gg.go.kr/dmz-imjingak
        \nInternational Cultural Service Club website: www.tourdmz.com
        \nKorea Travel Bureau Inc. website: www.go2korea.co.kr
        \nJoongang Express Tour website: jsatour.com
        \nPanmunjeom Travel Center website: www.koreadmztour.com
    </string>

    <!-- Bukhansan National Park -->
    <string name="bukhansan">Bukhansan National Park</string>
    <string name="bukhansan_short">Bukhansan National Park is a rare urban park in the world.
        It preserves beautiful natural scenery and cultural resources.</string>
    <string name="bukhansan_des">Bukhansan National Park is made up of huge granite. There are
        dozens of beautiful valleys between the main peaks, more than 1,300 species of flora and fauna
        are inhabited. It provides a variety of sights and ecological learning places.</string>
    <string name="bukhansan_address">215, Bogukmun-ro, Seongbuk-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea</string>
    <string name="bukhansan_transport">Gireum Station (Subway Line 4), Exit 3. Take Bus 110B or 143, and get off at the last bus stop.</string>
    <string name="bukhansan_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;909&#8211;0498</string>
    <string name="bukhansan_web">bukhan.knps.or.kr</string>
    <string name="bukhansan_hours">Open all year round</string>
    <string name="bukhansan_fee">Free</string>

    <!-- National Museum of Korea -->
    <string name="national_museum">National Museum of Korea</string>
    <string name="national_museum_short">The National Museum of Korea is the largest museum in
        Korea and houses precious Korean cultural assets that tell the story of Korea’s fascinating
        history, from ancient times to the modern era.</string>
    <string name="national_museum_des">In National Museum of Korea, more than 12,044 pieces are
        always on display in our six permanent exhibition sections. Visitors can examine numerous
        national treasures of Korea, including Pensive Bodhisattva (Korean National Treasure No.78
        or No.83), Goryeo Celadon Openwork Burner (No.95), Ten-Story Pagoda from Gyeongcheonsa
        Temple-Site (No.86), and Gold Crown from Silla (No.191).</string>
    <string name="national_museum_address">137, Seobinggo-ro, Yongsan-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="national_museum_transport">Ichon Station (Seoul Line 4 &amp;Gyeongui-Jungang
        Line), Exit 2</string>
    <string name="national_museum_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;2077&#8211;9000</string>
    <string name="national_museum_web">www.museum.go.kr/site/eng/home</string>
    <string name="national_museum_hours">Mon, Tue, Thu, Fri 10:00-18:00\nWed &amp; Sat
        10:00-21:00\nSun &amp; Public Holidays 10:00-19:00 </string>
    <string name="national_museum_fee">Free (except for special exhibitions)</string>

    <!-- Yeouido Hangang Park -->
    <string name="hangang_park">Yeouido Hangang Park</string>
    <string name="hangang_park_short">There are 12 Hangang Citizens\' Park, located along the
        Han River(Hangang). The Yeouido Hangang Park is the most popular spot for locals and tourists alike.</string>
    <string name="hangang_park_des">Yeouido Hangang Park is a leisure place where citizens can
        relax. It is a great place for picnics or cycling. There is a public bicycle rental center
        next to Exit 1 of Yeouido Station. There are many events to enjoy such as spring flower
        festival, world fireworks festival, various performances, and marathon events.</string>
    <string name="hangang_park_address">330, Yeouidong-ro, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="hangang_park_transport">Yeouinaru Station (Subway Line 5), Exit 2, 3</string>
    <string name="hangang_park_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;3780&#8211;0561</string>
    <string name="hangang_park_web">http://hangang.seoul.go.kr/park_yoido/</string>
    <string name="hangang_park_hours">Open all year round</string>
    <string name="hangang_park_fee">Free</string>

    <!-- Grevin museum -->
    <string name="grevin_museum">Grevin Museum</string>
    <string name="grevin_museum_short">Grevin Museum Seoul is a wax museum, displaying the waxworks
        of famous and historic people.</string>
    <string name="grevin_museum_des">The Grevin Museum has 133 years of history and locations
        in Paris, Prague, and Montreal. The opening of the Seoul location is the museum\'s 4th
        location worldwide and the first in Asia. \n\nWax figures include celebrities such as John
        Lennon, Marilyn Monroe, Tom Cruise, Psy, G-Dragon, Yuna Kim, and other Hallyu stars.
        King Sejong, Yi Sun-shin, and other historical figures are also represented at the museum.
        In total, there will be about 80 different wax figures.</string>
    <string name="grevin_museum_address">23, Eulji-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="grevin_museum_transport">Euljiro 1-ga Station (Subway Line 2), Exit 1&#8211;1</string>
    <string name="grevin_museum_phone">+82&#8211;70&#8211;4280&#8211;8749</string>
    <string name="grevin_museum_web">www.grevin-seoul.com/en/</string>
    <string name="grevin_museum_hours">09:30 ~ 19:00 (Fri, Sat 09:30 ~ 21:00)</string>
    <string name="grevin_museum_fee">Adults: 18,000 won</string>

    <!--Trick Eye Museum -->
    <string name="trickeye_museum">Trick Eye Museum</string>
    <string name="trickeye_museum_short">Trick Eye Museum is a new concept of exhibition space
        where culture and entertainment are combined. Visitors are invited to explore 3D optical
        illusion paintings and installations.</string>
    <string name="trickeye_museum_des">Trick Eye is shortened from \'Trick of the eye\' and
        refers to a traditional art technique Trompe-l\' oeil that turns two-dimensional paintings
        into three-dimensional images through the use of optical illusions. Paintings on museum walls,
        floors and ceilings come alive! Visitors are invited to step inside Trick Eye paintings and
        installations and create their own original stories.</string>
    <string name="trickeye_museum_address">Seogyo Plaza B2, 20, Hongik-ro 3-gil, Mapo-gu, Seoul, South Korea</string>
    <string name="trickeye_museum_transport">Hongik University Station (Subway Line 2), Exit 9</string>
    <string name="trickeye_museum_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;3144&#8211;6300</string>
    <string name="trickeye_museum_web">www.trickeye.com</string>
    <string name="trickeye_museum_hours">09:00 ~ 21:00</string>
    <string name="trickeye_museum_fee">Adults: 15,000 won</string>

    <!-- Olympic Park -->
    <string name="olympic_park">Olympic Park</string>
    <string name="olympic_park_short">The Olympic Park built for the 1988 Seoul Olympic Games
        is a multi-complex for sports, culture, and leisure.</string>
    <string name="olympic_park_des">Spread across approximately 1.45 million ㎡, Olympic Park
        encompasses the land that was once Mongchontoseong Fortress and Mongchonhaeja (manmade lake)
        from the early Baekje period. The park is divided into several zones: a leisure sports park,
        a cultural art park, an eco-park, and the History Experience Park dedicated to the area’s
        rich historic heritage. </string>
    <string name="olympic_park_address">424, Olympic-ro, Songpa-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="olympic_park_transport">Mongchontoseong Station (Subway Line8), Exit 1
        \nOlympic Park Station (Subway Line5), Exit 3</string>
    <string name="olympic_park_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;410&#8211;1114</string>
    <string name="olympic_park_web">www.olympicpark.co.kr</string>
    <string name="olympic_park_hours">Walking/Bicycle : 05:00 ~ 22:00 (~24:00 for Squares)\n
         Car : 06:00 ~ 22:00 \n※ For safety reasons, any entrance to all park property is NOT allowed
        except Peace Square and Meeting Square after 22:00.</string>
    <string name="olympic_park_fee">Free</string>

    <!-- Jamsil Baseball Stadium -->
    <string name="jamsil_baseball">Jamsil Baseball Stadium</string>
    <string name="jamsil_baseball_short">In Jamsil Baseball Stadium, visitors can experience
        the ardent fervor and cheering of Korean baseball fans.</string>
    <string name="jamsil_baseball_des">Jamsil Baseball Stadium is the home of two teams from
        the Korean Professional Baseball league, the LG Twins and the Doosan Bears. Even if you do
        not know about baseball, you can have a good time at Korean baseball stadium. There are lots
        of singing and dancing and all around good energy for the entire game. You can buy fried chicken
        and beer and other food. </string>
    <string name="jamsil_baseball_address">25, Olympic-ro, Songpa-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="jamsil_baseball_transport">Jamsil Sports Complex Station(Subway Line 2), Exit 5 or Exit 6</string>
    <string name="jamsil_baseball_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;2202&#8211;3852</string>
    <string name="jamsil_baseball_web">http://eng.koreabaseball.com\n
        ticket.interpark.com/contents/Promotion/Detail/gateway</string>
    <string name="jamsil_baseball_hours">KBO League : March 31 ~ September
        \nPost Season : October</string>
    <string name="jamsil_baseball_fee">Prices vary depending on location. 10,000 won ~ 20,000 won</string>

    <!-- National Folk Museum -->
    <string name="national_folk_museum">National Folk Museum of Korea</string>
    <string name="national_folk_museum_short">Adjacent to the Gyeongbokgung Palace, the National
        Folk Museum of Korea presents historical artifacts that were used in the daily lives of Korean
        people in the past.</string>
    <string name="national_folk_museum_des">The National Folk Museum of Korea has three permanent
        exhibitions and two special exhibitions as well as a library, souvenir shop, and other
        subsidiary facilities. Through the displays, visitors can learn about the domestic and
        agricultural lifestyles, as well as Korea’s cultural beliefs.</string>
    <string name="national_folk_museum_address">37, Samcheong-ro, Jongno-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="national_folk_museum_transport">Gyeongbokgung Station (Subway Line 3),
        Exit 5.\nAnguk Station (Subway Line 3), Exit 1.</string>
    <string name="national_folk_museum_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;3704&#8211;3114</string>
    <string name="national_folk_museum_web">www.nfm.go.kr</string>
    <string name="national_folk_museum_hours">March-May, September-October: 09:00-18:00\n
        June-August: 09:00-18:30\nNovember-February: 09:00-17:00\nWeekends &amp; public holidays
        (May-August): 09:00-19:00</string>
    <string name="national_folk_museum_fee">Free</string>

    <!-- COEX Aquarium -->
    <string name="coex_aquarium">COEX Aquarium</string>
    <string name="coex_aquarium_short">COEX Aquarium located in COEX shopping mall pursues an
        entertainment and education where anyone can discover and explore the marvelous ocean world.</string>
    <string name="coex_aquarium_des">The COEX aquarium houses 40,000 sea creatures, which come
        from 650 different species divided into 16 themed zones. The highest number of sharks and
        the largest variety of species in Korea are living in the aquarium.</string>
    <string name="coex_aquarium_address">513, Yeongdong-daero, Gangnam-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="coex_aquarium_transport">Bongeunsa Station (Subway Line 9), Exit 7\n
    Samseong Station (Subway Line 2), Exit 6</string>
    <string name="coex_aquarium_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;6002&#8211;6200</string>
    <string name="coex_aquarium_web">www.coexaqua.com/index_eng.asp</string>
    <string name="coex_aquarium_hours">10:00 ~ 20:00</string>
    <string name="coex_aquarium_fee">Adults : 28,000 won</string>

    <!-- Spa -->
    <string name="spa">Siloam Spa</string>
    <string name="spa_short">Siloam Spa, also known as Siloam Bulgama Sauna, is Korean Jjimjilbang.
    It is a place full of surprises and located within walking distance of Seoul Station.</string>
    <string name="spa_des">Siloam Spa is a kind of Jjimjilbang, Korean bathhouse. If you want to
        find inexpensive accommodation in Seoul, it may be the best choice. You can eat, sleep, and
        bath here. There are various fomentation rooms and after fomentation you will feel more relaxed.
    </string>
    <string name="spa_address">49, Jungnim-ro,Jung-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="spa_transport">Seoul Station(subway Line 1, 4), Exit 1</string>
    <string name="spa_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;364&#8211;3944</string>
    <string name="spa_web">www.silloamsauna.com</string>
    <string name="spa_hours">00:00 ~ 24:00  Open all year round </string>
    <string name="spa_fee">Daytime 10,000 won (includes Jjimjil)
        \nNighttime 15,000 won (includes Jjimjil)</string>

    <!-- Shopping -->
    <!-- Myeongdong -->
    <string name="myeongdong">Myeongdong</string>
    <string name="myeongdong_des">Myeong-dong is hottest shopping spot. There are tons of
        shops selling clothing, accessories, cosmetics, eyeglasses, and souvenirs. \n\nLotte department
        store, Shinsegae department store, several large shopping malls, and plenty of smaller shops
        offer the latest fashion items year-round. It is known as the to-go place for skincare and
        cosmetic brands.</string>
    <string name="myeongdong_address"> Myeongdong-gil, Jung-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="myeongdong_transport">Myeongdong Station (Subway Line 4), Exit 6\nEuljiro
        1-ga Station (Subway Line 2), Exit 6</string>
    <string name="myeongdong_hours">10:00 ~ 22:00</string>

    <!-- Namdaemun Market -->
    <string name="namdaemun">Namdaemun market</string>
    <string name="namdaemun_des">Namdaemun market is the largest traditional market in Korea
        with shops selling various goods. All products cost affordable prices and the stores
        in this area also function as wholesale markets.\n\nThe market sells a variety of clothes,
        glasses, kitchenware, toys, mountain gear, fishing equipment, stationery, fine arts,
        accessories, hats, carpets, flowers, ginseng, and imported goods.</string>
    <string name="namdaemun_address">21, Namdaemunsijang 4-gil, Jung-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="namdaemun_transport">Hoehyeon Station (Subway Line 4), Exit 5</string>
    <string name="namdaemun_hours">23:00 ~ 17:00 (the next day) ※ Opening hours will vary by shop.</string>

    <!-- Goto mall (Gangnam Terminal Underground Shopping Center -->
    <string name="goto_mall">Goto Mall</string>
    <string name="goto_mall_des">Goto Mall, also known as the Gangnam Terminal Underground Shopping Center,
        is 800 m long underground alley of accessories, skincare brands, shoes, clothes for all ages.
        This mall has over 600 stores. It is more popular among locals, and the price is reasonable.
        \n\n※ There are 3 rest areas. \n1) Near exit 1 ~ 4. \n2) Jungang Square between exit 7 and 8.
        \n3) West Square near exit 13 ~ 16</string>
    <string name="goto_mall_address">jiha 200, Sinbanpo-ro, Seocho-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="goto_mall_transport">Express Bus Terminal Station (Subway Line 3, 7, 9), Exit 8&#8211;1.</string>
    <string name="goto_mall_hours">10:00 ~ 22:00 (Varies by store.)</string>

    <!-- Dongdaemun -->
    <string name="dongdaemun">Dongdaemun Shopping Mall</string>
    <string name="dongdaemun_des">Dongdaemun is a large shopping district filled with many
        shopping malls, divided into wholesale and non-wholesale. The must-visit malls are Doota and
        Migliore which sells retail goods.
        \n\nDoota is one of the largest fashion malls full of trendy fashion items, unique and
        high-quality products. Migliore is a convenient facility that has an enormous variety of
        products sold at reasonable prices.</string>
    <string name="dongdaemun_address">Doota: 275, Jangchungdan-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul
        \nMigliore: 263, Jangchungdan-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="dongdaemun_transport">Dongdaemun History &amp; Culture Park Station (Subway Line
        2, 4, 5), Exit 14\nDongdaemun Station (Subway Line 1, 4), Exit 8</string>
    <string name="dongdaemun_hours">Doota: 10:30am ~ 12:00am (Extended till 5am on Fri &amp; Sat)
        \nMigliore : 10:30am ~ 4:30am (Closed on Mondays)</string>

    <!-- Common Ground -->
    <string name="common_ground">Common Ground</string>
    <string name="common_ground_des">Common Ground is the first artsy pop-up container mall in
        Korea and a great place to hang out and take pictures.\n\nMost of the shops are aimed at the
        young and sells the latest fashion, unique items, and accessories. It is divided into 5 areas,
        such as street market, market hall, terrace market, market ground, and food truck market.</string>
    <string name="common_ground_address">200, Achasan-ro, Gwangjin-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="common_ground_transport">Konkuk University Station (Subway Line 2 or 7), Exit 6</string>
    <string name="common_ground_hours">Store: 11:00 ~ 22:00 \nPub: 11:00 ~ 02:00</string>

    <!-- Garosugil -->
    <string name="garosu_gil">Garosugil</string>
    <string name="garosu_gil_des">Garosugil means tree-lined streets. Garosugil is a beautiful
        street with trendy fashion shops, prop shops, chic art galleries, restaurants, bars and great
        cafes along both sides. \n\nGarosugil is particularly lovely in autumn when the golden Gingko
        leaves begin to fall.</string>
    <string name="garosu_gil_address">Sinsa-dong, Gangnam-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="garosu_gil_transport">Sinsa Station (Subway Line 3), Exit 8</string>
    <string name="garosu_gil_hours">10:00 ~ 24:00</string>

    <!-- Times Square Mall -->
    <string name="times_square">Times Square Mall</string>
    <string name="times_square_des">Times Square is one of Seoul\'s largest shopping malls,
        including a Shinsegae department store, multiplex theater(CGV), E-Mart discount store, book
        store, hotel and restaurants. The shopping mall offers a relaxed and friendly natural
        environment such as a rest area, a terrace, a fountain and a garden.</string>
    <string name="times_square_address">15, Yeongjung-ro, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="times_square_transport">Yeongdeungpo Station (Subway Line 1), Exit 3</string>
    <string name="times_square_hours">10:30 ~ 22:00</string>

    <!-- Food -->
    <!-- Gwangjang Market -->
    <string name="gwangjang">Gwangjang Market</string>
    <string name="gwangjang_des">Gwangjang Market is the traditional market which is
        notable for foreign visitors to experience an authentic Korean culture especially street food.
        The most famous street foods are bindaetteok (Korean style pancake), Tteokbokki, Gimbap,
        Beef Tartare (called yukhoe), Beef Tartare Bibimbap, Sliced raw octopus.</string>
    <string name="gwangjang_address">88, Changgyeonggung-ro, Jongno-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="gwangjang_transport">Jongno 5-ga Station (Subway Line 1), Exit 8
        \nEuljiro 4-ga Station (Subway Line 2, 5), Exit 4</string>
    <string name="gwangjang_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;2267&#8211;0291</string>
    <string name="gwangjang_web">www.kwangjangmarket.co.kr/en/</string>
    <string name="gwangjang_hours">General stores 09:00 ~ 18:00 (※ Closed on Sundays)
        \nFood Street 09:00 ~ 23:00 (※ Open all year round)
        \nVintage shops 10:00 ~ 19:00(※ Closed on Sundays)
        \nHours vary by store.</string>
    <string name="gwangjang_fee">Bindaetteok: 4,000 won ~ 8,000 won
        \nGimbap: 3,000 won\nBeef Tartare: 15,000 won</string>

    <!-- Hanilkwan -->
    <string name="hanilkwan">Hanilkwan</string>
    <string name="hanilkwan_des">Hanilkwan, founded in 1939, serves the typical Seoul cuisine.
        The menus are Korean barbecue, Grilled chadol-baeggi, Roast pyunchae, Platter of nine delicacies,
        Stir-fried baby octopus, Goldongban and so on. They offer a course meal with original Korean
        food. It is a little more expensive than other restaurants.
        \nThere are other branches in addition to Apgujeong and Yeongdeungpo.</string>
    <string name="hanilkwan_address">Yeongdeungpo(Times Square Mall 4F): 15, Yeongjung-ro,
        Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="hanilkwan_transport">Yeongdeungpo: Yeongdeungpo Station (Subway Line 1),
        Exit 3\nApgujeong: Apgujeong Station (Subway Line 2), Exit 2</string>
    <string name="hanilkwan_phone">+82&#8211;1577&#8211;9963</string>
    <string name="hanilkwan_web">www.hanilkwan.co.kr (Korean, English)</string>
    <string name="hanilkwan_hours">Yeongdeungpo: 11:30 ~ 22:30\nApgujeong: 11:30 ~ 21:30</string>
    <string name="hanilkwan_fee">Bansan Soup &amp; Rice Noodle Special: 13,000 ~ 17,000won
        \nBansang Grill Lunch: 21,000 ~ 22,000won
        \nBansang Grill Special: 37,000 ~ 61,000won (These menus differ depending on which branch you choose.)</string>

    <!-- Tosokchon Samgyetang -->
    <string name="tosokchon">Tosokchon Samgyetang</string>
    <string name="tosokchon_des">Tosokchon Samgyetang, located near Gyeongbokgung, is a chicken
        soup made by adding luxurious ginseng and glutinous rice, pumpkin seed, black sesame, walnut,
        pine, native chestnut, medicinal jujube, ginkgo nut, garlic, sunflower seeds, and secret
        ingredients.</string>
    <string name="tosokchon_address">5, Jahamun-ro 5-gil, Jongno-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="tosokchon_transport">Gyeongbokgung Station (Subway Line 3), Exit 2. After
        getting out of the Exit 2, go straight 120m and it\'s on the lef alley of GS25.</string>
    <string name="tosokchon_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;737&#8211;7444</string>
    <string name="tosokchon_web">www.tosokchon.co.kr</string>
    <string name="tosokchon_hours">10:00 ~ 22:00</string>
    <string name="tosokchone_fee">Tosokchon Samgyetang : 16,000won</string>

    <!-- Manjok ohyang jokbal -->
    <string name="jokbal">Manjok Ohyang Jokbal</string>
    <string name="jokbal_des">Manjok Ohyang Jokbal features jokbal (pig\'s trotter) served with
        sliced cabbage and specialty garlic sauce to eat together. Also, bul-jokbal (spicy pig\'s
        trotter) is a famous menu item that gets its spicy taste from cheongyang red pepper powder
        and is served with bossam (steamed pork) cooked with special meat stock and boiled every day.
    </string>
    <string name="jokbal_address">134&#8211;7, Seosomun-ro, Jung-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="jokbal_transport">City Hall Station (Seoul Subway Line 1 &amp; 2), Exit 8.
        \nGo down Seosomun-gil Street, which has a pharmacy on the left side. After walking 30m, you
        will see a building on the right side with ‘jokbal, mandu’ written on it. Manjok Ohyang
        Jokbal restaurant is on the 2nd floor of this building, above a restaurant called Cheongsol.</string>
    <string name="jokbal_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;753&#8211;4755</string>
    <string name="jokbal_web">www.manjok.net (Korean only)</string>
    <string name="jokbal_hours">Weekdays 11:30 ~ 22:00\nWeekends 12:00 ~ 22:00\n※ Operating
        hours and closed days are subject to changes. Make a phone-inquiry before visiting.</string>
    <string name="jokbal_fee">Manjok Ohyang Jokbal: 32,000won</string>

    <!-- Better than Beef -->
    <string name="better_than_beef">Better than Beef</string>
    <string name="better_than_beef_des">Better than Beef is a special pork belly fusion restaurant
        located in Garosugil, Shinsa-dong. There are unique menus such as Variety Samgyeopsal
        (pork belly), cheese tofu and creamy toast pork. Variety Samgyeopsal dish consists of
        cream sauce, jalapeno, sliced potato, cheese and of course well-cooked Samgyeopsal.
        \n\nBetter than Beef also sells all kinds of homemade rice wine, called Makgeolli with distinct
        flavors, such as ricotta cheese and blueberry.</string>
    <string name="better_than_beef_address">5, Dosan-daero11-Gil, Seoul</string>
    <string name="better_than_beef_transport">Shinsa Station (Subway Line 3), Exit 8</string>
    <string name="better_than_beef_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;3446&#8211;0400</string>
    <string name="better_than_beef_hours">11:30 ~ 24:00 (last order - 21:30 ~ 22:00)
        \nSat 12:00 ~ 24:00\nSun 12:00 ~ 23:00</string>
    <string name="better_than_beef_fee">13,000won ~ 29,000won</string>

    <!-- Daedo Sikdang -->
    <string name="daedo">Daedo Sikdang</string>
    <string name="daedo_des">Daedo Sikdang is a Korean beef (also called Hanwoo) restaurant.
        The menu is just one item, Korean beef Sirloin. The restaurant serves sirloin steak
        which is well-aged and has a clear marbling of fat throughout the flesh. The meat is super
        tender and juicy.</string>
    <string name="daedo_address">3, Muhak-ro 12-gil, Seongdong-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="daedo_transport">Sangwangsimni Station (Subway Line 2), Exit 2</string>
    <string name="daedo_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;2292&#8211;9772</string>
    <string name="daedo_web">eng.kitchenborie.com</string>
    <string name="daedo_hours">11:00 ~ 22:00</string>
    <string name="daedo_fee">Hanwoo sirloin (200g): 38,500won</string>

    <!-- Fried chicken -->
    <string name="chicken">Fried Chicken delivery</string>
    <string name="chicken_des">Chimaek refers to a combination of chicken and beer. "chi" for
        chicken and "maek" for maekju, Korean for beer. Eating chicken with beer is Chimaek.
        \n\nOne of the highlights of Korean chicken is delivery culture is on another level.
        They deliver to you by the side of the river, at a park, wherever you want. There is a
        variety of delivery chicken brand, such as BHC, Kyochon, BBQ, Nene, Goobne, Yellow whole
        chicken and so on. You can deliver BHC, Nene, Goobne, and other brands in English by using
        Shuttle Delivery services. </string>
    <string name="chicken_address">Set your Location</string>
    <string name="chicken_phone">1661&#8211;8482</string>
    <string name="chicken_web">www.shuttledelivery.co.kr/en</string>
    <string name="chicken_hours">Mon - Fri 11:30 ~ 15:00&amp;16:30 ~ 21:30
        \nSat &amp; Sun 11:30 ~ 21:30</string>
    <string name="chicken_fee">15,000won ~ 20,000won</string>

    <!-- Jungsik-->
    <string name="jungsik">Jungsik</string>
    <string name="jungsik_des">Jungsik is a two-Michelin starred restaurant in Seoul and New York,
        serving contemporary, creative Korean Cuisine. Owner Chef Jungsik Yim reinvents Korean
        cuisine using traditional and familiar ingredients, creating a brand-new genre of food:
        New Korean Fine Dining.</string>
    <string name="jungsik_address">11, Seolleung-ro 158-gil, Gangnamgu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="jungsik_transport">Apgugeongrodeo Station (Bundang Line), Exit 4</string>
    <string name="jungsik_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;517&#8211;4654</string>
    <string name="jungsik_web">www.jungsik.kr/</string>
    <string name="jungsik_hours">12:00 ~ 22:00 ※ Break time 15:00 ~ 17:30</string>
    <string name="jungsik_fee">Lunch: 60,000 ~ 150,000won\nDinner: 100,000 ~ 180,000won</string>

    <!-- Beef of Love -->
    <string name="beef_sarang">Beef of Love</string>
    <string name="beef_sarang_des">Beef of Love is very modern and atmospheric unlike to other
        Korean BBQ restaurants. This restaurant specializes in Korean beef, Hanwoo, especially
        sirloin (Deungshim) and tenderloin (Anshim). You can have grilled steak with Truffle salt
        and cheese. The owner cooks the meat to perfection. </string>
    <string name="beef_sarang_address">106, Hannam-daero, Yongsan-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="beef_sarang_transport">Hangangjin Station (Subway Line 6), Exit 3</string>
    <string name="beef_sarang_phone">+82&#8211;2&#8211;794&#8211;3313</string>
    <string name="beef_sarang_web">beefsarang.modod.at(Korean only)</string>
    <string name="beef_sarang_hours">17:30 ~ 11:00 ※ Closed on Sundays</string>
    <string name="beef_sarang_fee">Prices are subject to change.</string>

    <!-- Bamdokkaebi Night Market -->
    <string name="bamdokkaebi">Yeoido Bamdokkaebi Night Market </string>
    <string name="bamdokkaebi_des">Bamdokkaebi Night Market is a new type of space that incorporates
        a variety of concepts and exists for only a finite amount of time. There is the Food Truck Zone where
        you can discover diverse foods from all over the world. Since there are lots of food to choose, the best
        indication may be the longest queue.</string>
    <string name="bamdokkaebi_address">330, Yeouidong-ro, Yeongdeungpo-gu, Seoul</string>
    <string name="bamdokkaebi_transport">Yeouinaru Station (Subway Line 5), Exit 2 (walk approx. 600 m)</string>
    <string name="bamdokkaebi_web">www.bamdokkaebi.org</string>
    <string name="bamdokkaebi_hours">Fri &amp; Sat: 18:00 ~ 23:00 (From late March to late October)</string>
    <string name="bamdokkaebi_fee">5,000won ~ 10,000won</string>

    <!-- Korean Fragment -->
    <string name="hello">Hello.</string>
    <string name="hello_p">An-nyeong-ha-se-yo</string>
    <string name="hello_k">안녕하세요?</string>

    <string name="nice_to_meet_you">Nice to meet you.</string>
    <string name="nice_to_meet_you_p">Man-na-seo ban-gab-seub-ni-da.</string>
    <string name="nice_to_meet_you_k">만나서 반갑습니다.</string>

    <string name="thank_you">Thank you.</string>
    <string name="thank_you_p">Gam-sa-ham-ni-da.</string>
    <string name="thank_you_k">감사합니다.</string>

    <string name="good_bye">Good bye.(said to somebody not departing)</string>
    <string name="good_bye_p">An-nyeong-hi gye-se-yo.</string>
    <string name="good_bye_k">안녕히 계세요.</string>

    <string name="i_am_sorry">I\'m sorry.</string>
    <string name="i_am_sorry_p">Jweh-song-ham-ni-da</string>
    <string name="i_am_sorry_k">죄송합니다.</string>

    <string name="how_much_is_this">How much is this?</string>
    <string name="how_much_is_this_p">Eol-ma-ye-yo?</string>
    <string name="how_much_is_this_k">얼마예요?</string>

    <string name="picture">Could you take a picture of me, please?</string>
    <string name="picture_p">Sajin jom jjig-eo ju-si-ge-sseo-yo?</string>
    <string name="picture_k">사진 좀 찍어 주시겠어요?</string>

    <string name="where_is_the_restroom">Where is the restroom?</string>
    <string name="where_is_the_restroom_p">Hwa-jang-sil-eun eo-di-e i-sseo-yo?</string>
    <string name="where_is_the_restroom_k">화장실은 어디에 있어요?</string>

    <string name="how_to_get_to_gangnam">Could you tell me how to get to Gangnam?</string>
    <string name="how_to_get_to_gangnam_p">Gangnam-Kka-ji eo-tteo-ke ga-yo?</string>
    <string name="how_to_get_to_gangnam_k">강남까지 어떻게 가요?</string>
    
    <string name="how_far">How far is it from here?</string>
    <string name="how_far_p">Yeo-gi-seo eul-ma-na meom-ni-kka?</string>
    <string name="how_far_k">여기서 얼마나 멉니까?</string>


</resources>
